{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772500930","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772500930"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 962481fa-d843-4b00-b049-faf63b0a9f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwangu_wazi-gari-mwangu-yeyote"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mwangu"," userResponse":" gari"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772504564","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772504564"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 962481fa-d843-4b00-b049-faf63b0a9f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwangu_wazi-gari-mwangu-yeyote"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mwangu"," userResponse":" wazi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772508317","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772508317"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 962481fa-d843-4b00-b049-faf63b0a9f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwangu_wazi-gari-mwangu-yeyote"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mwangu"," userResponse":" mwangu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772544794","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772544794"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 962481fa-d843-4b00-b049-faf63b0a9f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zaidi_zaidi-kwamba-pia-ndege"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" zaidi"," userResponse":" ndege"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772548063","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772548063"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 962481fa-d843-4b00-b049-faf63b0a9f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zaidi_zaidi-kwamba-pia-ndege"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" zaidi"," userResponse":" zaidi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772593477","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772593477"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 962481fa-d843-4b00-b049-faf63b0a9f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtini_uchungu-mtini-mumbi-punde"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mtini"," userResponse":" punde"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772596363","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772596363"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 962481fa-d843-4b00-b049-faf63b0a9f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mtini_uchungu-mtini-mumbi-punde"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mtini"," userResponse":" mtini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772658885","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772658883"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 962481fa-d843-4b00-b049-faf63b0a9f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mtini_uchungu-mtini-mumbi-punde"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772659039","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772659038"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 962481fa-d843-4b00-b049-faf63b0a9f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772736361","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772736361"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 962481fa-d843-4b00-b049-faf63b0a9f57"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_29"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Sasa hivi lazima niende zangu nyumbani mbali na Upepo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772736419","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772736419"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" b7703e5a-79d2-48fa-86cd-a0119ef5e3c8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_30"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ng'ombe alilipa nauli ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772747368","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772747367"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" omba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" OMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772751363","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772751363"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" omba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772752959","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772752958"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772756620","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772756619"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772758243","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772758243"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" ONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772761436","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772761436"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772763064","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772763063"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" oa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772766237","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772766237"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" oa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772767853","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772767853"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" osha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" OSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772771338","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772771337"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" osha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OSHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772772952","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772772951"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ofisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" OFISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772776844","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772776844"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ofisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772778447","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772778447"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772782485","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772782485"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772784513","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772784512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772784766","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772784766"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..4.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772795815","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772795815"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772804346","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772804346"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 0cc216d2-d452-4c0b-861b-ce22f67d72e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772815170","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772815170"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772815703","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772815703"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772815929","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772815929"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772816633","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772816632"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772817710","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772817710"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772818654","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772818654"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772819463","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772819463"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772820287","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772820287"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772824165","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772824164"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUGOMBANA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUGOMBANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772825001","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772824999"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772825612","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772825612"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772828223","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772828223"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772829503","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772829502"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWASAIDIA"," userResponse":" WALIWASAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772830298","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772830297"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772831206","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772831205"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772831691","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772831690"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772832574","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772832574"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" SHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772835943","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772835942"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772837471","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772837470"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATAZWA"," userResponse":" WALIKATAZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772837934","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772837934"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772838613","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772838612"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772838830","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772838830"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772839438","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772839437"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772842860","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772842859"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772843332","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772843331"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772843828","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772843827"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772844822","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772844822"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772845743","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772845743"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772848597","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772848597"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772848850","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772848850"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772849024","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772849024"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772849678","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772849678"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772850752","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772850751"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772851626","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772851626"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEUMBWA"," userResponse":" WAMEUMBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772851949","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772851949"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772852483","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772852483"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772855842","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772855842"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772856504","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772856504"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANA"," userResponse":" KIJANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772857199","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772857198"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772858242","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772858242"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772858700","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772858700"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772859400","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772859399"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772860377","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772860377"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772860621","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772860621"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772861315","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772861313"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANA"," userResponse":" MCHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772864341","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772864341"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772864896","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772864896"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772865840","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772865840"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772866053","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772866052"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772866495","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772866494"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772866928","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772866927"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772868271","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772868271"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAZIDI"," userResponse":" IKAZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772870960","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772870959"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772872011","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772872011"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONYA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772872766","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772872765"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIENDE"," userResponse":" ASIENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772873564","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772873563"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUANI"," userResponse":" JUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772876564","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772876563"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772877938","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772877938"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUSIKIA"," userResponse":" HAKUSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772881467","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772881466"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEYUKA"," userResponse":" ALIYEYUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772881719","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772881718"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772882311","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772882310"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772882758","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772882757"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772883473","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772883472"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772884299","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772884298"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" KALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772887516","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772887515"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772887754","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772887753"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772888107","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772888107"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772889662","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772889661"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" WALIHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772890880","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772890879"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOONA"," userResponse":" WALIPOONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772891328","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772891327"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772891813","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772891812"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772893087","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772893087"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIYEYUKA"," userResponse":" AKIYEYUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772896544","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772896544"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAPANGA"," userResponse":" WAKAPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772896955","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772896954"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772897693","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772897692"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANI"," userResponse":" FULANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772900557","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772900557"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHUKUA"," userResponse":" WALICHUKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772901150","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772901150"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772902460","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772902458"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOYEYUKA"," userResponse":" ILIYOYEYUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772903940","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772903939"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATENGEZA"," userResponse":" WAKATENGEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772904497","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772904496"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772907874","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772907873"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWEKA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772908415","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772908415"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772908878","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772908877"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772909333","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772909332"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772909602","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772909601"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772910225","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772910224"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772910970","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772910969"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772913969","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772913968"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772915358","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772915357"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOCHOMOZA"," userResponse":" LILIPOCHOMOZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772916604","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772916603"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772918680","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772918679"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPEPERUKA"," userResponse":" AKAPEPERUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772919875","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772919875"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" AKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772920232","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772920231"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772921105","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772921104"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772923712","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772923711"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772923792","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772923792"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772949639","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772949639"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772959912","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772959912"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" de46d143-b5eb-40b1-b89d-3d8d1ce00c5a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772973021","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772973021"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" d291d14e-d7a4-4680-b503-5e02cb2af559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-m-u"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772978262","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772978262"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" d291d14e-d7a4-4680-b503-5e02cb2af559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-t-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772982112","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772982112"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" d291d14e-d7a4-4680-b503-5e02cb2af559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_h-p-o"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772985501","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772985500"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" d291d14e-d7a4-4680-b503-5e02cb2af559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_t-o-v"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772989078","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772989078"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" d291d14e-d7a4-4680-b503-5e02cb2af559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_y-o-v"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772992475","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772992475"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" d291d14e-d7a4-4680-b503-5e02cb2af559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-e-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772996002","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772996002"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" d291d14e-d7a4-4680-b503-5e02cb2af559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_f-m-o"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543772999280","data":{"timestamp":" 1543772999280"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" d291d14e-d7a4-4680-b503-5e02cb2af559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-a-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773002703","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773002702"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" d291d14e-d7a4-4680-b503-5e02cb2af559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-w-t"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773006272","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773006272"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" d291d14e-d7a4-4680-b503-5e02cb2af559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_ch-o-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773012057","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773012055"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" d291d14e-d7a4-4680-b503-5e02cb2af559"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_o_ch-o-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773029633","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773029633"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 10b878e9-c306-4e12-ae14-abe7c9d7d963"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_t-o-v"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773032825","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773032825"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 10b878e9-c306-4e12-ae14-abe7c9d7d963"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_y-o-v"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773036504","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773036504"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 10b878e9-c306-4e12-ae14-abe7c9d7d963"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-m-u"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773040024","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773040024"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 10b878e9-c306-4e12-ae14-abe7c9d7d963"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_f-m-o"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773043147","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773043147"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 10b878e9-c306-4e12-ae14-abe7c9d7d963"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-e-r"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773046223","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773046223"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 10b878e9-c306-4e12-ae14-abe7c9d7d963"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-a-h"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773049401","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773049400"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 10b878e9-c306-4e12-ae14-abe7c9d7d963"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-t-b"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773052918","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773052918"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 10b878e9-c306-4e12-ae14-abe7c9d7d963"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_h-p-o"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773056402","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773056402"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 10b878e9-c306-4e12-ae14-abe7c9d7d963"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_ch-o-e"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773059692","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773059692"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 10b878e9-c306-4e12-ae14-abe7c9d7d963"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-w-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773065453","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773065452"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 10b878e9-c306-4e12-ae14-abe7c9d7d963"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_O..O.all.rand.all.stat.show.106"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-w-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773076320","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773076320"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773076878","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773076878"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773078382","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773078381"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773079286","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773079286"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" ALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773080009","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773080009"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773080487","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773080486"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773081280","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773081280"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773084339","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773084338"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773084551","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773084551"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773085032","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773085032"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773085946","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773085945"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773087726","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773087726"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TULIJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773088510","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773088510"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" LINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773089053","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773089053"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773090468","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773090468"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGETUGAWIA"," userResponse":" ANGETUGAWIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773091301","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773091300"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773091866","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773091866"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773095336","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773095335"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773096676","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773096675"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKANGU"," userResponse":" KAKANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773097984","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773097983"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773099653","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773099652"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773102499","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773102499"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYALA"," userResponse":" ALIYALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773103321","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773103321"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773103604","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773103604"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773104561","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773104559"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773105666","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773105665"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773105931","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773105931"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773108900","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773108900"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773109150","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773109150"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773109641","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773109641"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773110368","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773110368"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773111781","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773111781"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773113768","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773113768"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULILIA"," userResponse":" TULILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773115269","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773115269"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISEMA"," userResponse":" TUKISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773116755","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773116755"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773116944","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773116943"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773118078","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773118077"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTUKUTU"," userResponse":" MTUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773119122","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773119121"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773119371","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773119371"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773120385","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773120384"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHOYO"," userResponse":" MCHOYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773123273","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773123273"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773125033","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773125033"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773126379","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773126379"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773127860","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773127859"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773128571","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773128570"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773130109","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773130109"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773130968","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773130968"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773132607","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773132607"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773133974","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773133974"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMELIWA"," userResponse":" YAMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773136821","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773136820"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773137056","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773137055"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773137544","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773137544"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773138287","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773138286"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773140045","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773140045"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" TULIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773140799","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773140799"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773141455","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773141455"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773142230","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773142229"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773143082","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773143082"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773146657","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773146657"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULMWULIZA"," userResponse":" TULMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773147358","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773147358"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773148540","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773148539"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773150016","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773150012"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," userResponse":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773150660","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773150659"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773154144","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773154144"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773155007","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773155007"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773156170","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773156170"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773157635","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773157634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773158467","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773158467"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773160404","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773160403"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," userResponse":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773163615","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773163614"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773164927","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773164927"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773166046","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773166046"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" KUTULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773167338","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773167337"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773168097","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773168096"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773171102","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773171101"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773172666","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773172665"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773173583","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773173583"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773173844","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773173843"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773174689","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773174688"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773174836","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773174836"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773175550","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773175549"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773177073","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773177073"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAUMWA"," userResponse":" NAUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773177401","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773177401"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773178120","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773178119"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773181855","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773181855"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773182764","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773182763"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TULIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773183445","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773183445"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773184469","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773184469"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773185263","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773185263"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773186028","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773186028"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773186959","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773186958"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773188076","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773188076"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773188547","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773188546"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773189395","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773189395"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773190755","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773190753"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGECHAPWA"," userResponse":" ANGECHAPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773190959","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773190958"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773191466","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773191465"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773194913","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773194912"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773196279","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773196278"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPOPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773196947","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773196946"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFUU"," userResponse":" NAFUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773198542","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773198542"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773199835","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773199834"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUOMBA"," userResponse":" ALITUOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773201066","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773201066"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773203691","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773203689"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773203774","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773203774"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" a0a29463-4f41-4a2f-89f7-f01fd93980bf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773216777","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773216776"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773217331","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773217331"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773218844","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773218843"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773219768","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773219768"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" ALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773220507","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773220506"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773220991","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773220991"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773221799","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773221798"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773224902","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773224902"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773225123","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773225123"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773225608","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773225608"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773226532","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773226531"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773228295","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773228295"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TULIJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773229075","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773229075"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" LINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773229629","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773229628"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773231051","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773231050"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGETUGAWIA"," userResponse":" ANGETUGAWIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773231888","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773231887"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773232454","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773232454"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773235931","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773235931"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773237275","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773237274"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKANGU"," userResponse":" KAKANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773238569","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773238568"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773240231","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773240230"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773243126","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773243123"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYALA"," userResponse":" ALIYALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773243956","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773243956"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773244240","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773244239"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773245192","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773245192"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773246302","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773246301"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773246561","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773246561"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773249567","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773249566"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773249819","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773249819"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773250309","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773250309"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773251046","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773251046"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773252468","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773252467"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773254467","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773254467"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULILIA"," userResponse":" TULILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773255961","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773255960"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISEMA"," userResponse":" TUKISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773257448","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773257447"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773257640","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773257640"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773258776","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773258775"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTUKUTU"," userResponse":" MTUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773259820","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773259820"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773260072","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773260072"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773261087","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773261087"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHOYO"," userResponse":" MCHOYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773263955","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773263954"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773265701","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773265700"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773267031","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773267031"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773268509","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773268509"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773269230","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773269230"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773270753","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773270753"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773271623","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773271622"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773273261","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773273261"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773274642","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773274642"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMELIWA"," userResponse":" YAMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773277510","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773277510"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773277741","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773277741"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773278215","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773278214"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773278959","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773278959"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773280711","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773280710"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" TULIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773281474","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773281473"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773282134","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773282134"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773282903","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773282903"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773283761","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773283761"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773287316","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773287315"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULMWULIZA"," userResponse":" TULMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773288018","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773288018"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773289189","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773289189"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773290652","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773290652"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," userResponse":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773291292","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773291292"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773294794","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773294793"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773295647","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773295647"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773296811","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773296811"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773298268","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773298267"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773299091","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773299091"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773301018","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773301017"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," userResponse":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773304190","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773304190"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773305493","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773305492"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773306595","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773306595"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" KUTULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773307868","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773307867"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773308635","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773308634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773311666","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773311665"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773313240","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773313240"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773314155","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773314155"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773314417","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773314416"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773315262","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773315261"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773315403","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773315403"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773316097","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773316097"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773317620","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773317620"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAUMWA"," userResponse":" NAUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773317941","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773317941"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773318662","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773318661"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773322347","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773322346"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773323266","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773323266"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TULIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773323951","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773323950"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773324971","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773324970"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773325771","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773325771"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773326542","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773326542"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773327468","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773327468"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773328585","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773328584"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773329047","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773329047"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773329896","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773329895"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773331258","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773331257"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGECHAPWA"," userResponse":" ANGECHAPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773331465","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773331465"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773331970","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773331970"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773335509","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773335509"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773336870","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773336870"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPOPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773337543","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773337543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFUU"," userResponse":" NAFUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773339128","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773339128"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773340441","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773340441"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUOMBA"," userResponse":" ALITUOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773341677","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773341676"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773344291","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773344290"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773344394","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773344394"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" c2403445-92dd-4497-a045-6936e4f0c62c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773353047","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773353047"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773356645","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773356645"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773360507","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773360507"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773365302","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773365301"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773369113","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773369113"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773372320","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773372320"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773375780","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773375779"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773379993","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773379992"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773383250","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773383250"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773386676","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773386676"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773390513","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773390513"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773394667","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773394667"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773398342","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773398342"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773402412","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773402412"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773405736","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773405736"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773410916","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773410916"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773414660","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773414660"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773418335","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773418335"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773423558","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773423558"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773426756","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773426756"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773429994","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773429994"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773433969","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773433969"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773437756","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773437756"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773441312","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773441311"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773447118","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773447118"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 92aa4eb0-05fd-4d89-a7e7-3f5858e29a8e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773458777","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773458777"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 4dfe074a-bcd5-4b89-b997-eb43dc7d6d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773464459","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773464459"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 4dfe074a-bcd5-4b89-b997-eb43dc7d6d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773469406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773469406"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 4dfe074a-bcd5-4b89-b997-eb43dc7d6d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-3-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773475242","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773475242"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 4dfe074a-bcd5-4b89-b997-eb43dc7d6d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-3-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773482171","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773482171"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 4dfe074a-bcd5-4b89-b997-eb43dc7d6d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773489076","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773489076"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 4dfe074a-bcd5-4b89-b997-eb43dc7d6d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-4-3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773498536","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773498536"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 4dfe074a-bcd5-4b89-b997-eb43dc7d6d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-2-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773505543","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773505543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 4dfe074a-bcd5-4b89-b997-eb43dc7d6d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773513046","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773513045"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 4dfe074a-bcd5-4b89-b997-eb43dc7d6d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773519533","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773519532"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 4dfe074a-bcd5-4b89-b997-eb43dc7d6d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773525816","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773525814"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 4dfe074a-bcd5-4b89-b997-eb43dc7d6d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773532337","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773532336"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 4dfe074a-bcd5-4b89-b997-eb43dc7d6d18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773546971","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773546971"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773547559","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773547558"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773548292","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773548292"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773548472","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773548471"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773549250","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773549250"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" MATATIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773550283","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773550282"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773553147","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773553145"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPANGA"," userResponse":" TULIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773553842","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773553842"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOLENI"," userResponse":" FOLENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773555111","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773555111"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773556784","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773556784"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUKISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773557517","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773557517"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOTA"," userResponse":" KUCHOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773558367","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773558367"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773559241","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773559241"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773559973","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773559973"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773560644","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773560643"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773564239","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773564238"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TULISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773564779","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773564778"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773564922","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773564921"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773565329","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773565329"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773566169","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773566168"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773567089","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773567089"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOKEA"," userResponse":" KUPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773567781","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773567781"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773567943","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773567943"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773568708","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773568708"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773571793","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773571791"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFUNGA"," userResponse":" TULIFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773572273","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773572273"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773572798","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773572797"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773573579","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773573578"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773574241","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773574241"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773574883","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773574883"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773574967","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773574967"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773575571","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773575570"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIZI"," userResponse":" WIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773578768","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773578768"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773578907","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773578907"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773579851","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773579850"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773580928","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773580928"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" WALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773581596","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773581596"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773582047","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773582046"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773582682","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773582681"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773583236","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773583236"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773583733","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773583733"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773585116","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773585114"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773585777","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773585777"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPA"," userResponse":" KULIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773586374","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773586374"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" KARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773589394","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773589394"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773589774","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773589773"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773590767","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773590766"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773591279","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773591278"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773592244","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773592243"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773592903","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773592902"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773593537","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773593537"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYA"," userResponse":" YAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773596584","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773596583"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773597349","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773597348"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773598175","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773598175"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRANDA"," userResponse":" WALIRANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773598669","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773598669"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANDA"," userResponse":" RANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773599613","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773599613"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773600255","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773600255"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773600871","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773600870"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773601814","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773601813"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYIA"," userResponse":" WAKIFANYIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773602265","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773602265"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773602753","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773602753"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773603729","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773603729"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHAMBANI"," userResponse":" MASHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773606825","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773606824"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773608138","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773608138"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOVUMA"," userResponse":" ULIPOVUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773609882","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773609882"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773610703","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773610703"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773611551","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773611551"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAFU"," userResponse":" CHAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773612032","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773612032"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773613260","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773613259"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZIANGIKA"," userResponse":" KUZIANGIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773614301","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773614300"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" MITINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773614770","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773614770"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773615397","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773615397"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UANI"," userResponse":" UANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773618797","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773618797"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773619404","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773619404"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773620351","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773620351"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATWA"," userResponse":" WALIKATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773620543","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773620543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773621292","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773621291"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" VIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773621542","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773621542"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773622176","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773622175"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773623570","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773623570"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773623923","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773623923"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773624406","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773624406"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773627902","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773627902"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773628352","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773628352"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773629010","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773629009"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773630309","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773630309"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773630513","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773630512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773631130","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773631129"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773632354","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773632354"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAUKA"," userResponse":" ULIKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773633053","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773633052"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773633930","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773633930"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITUNGI"," userResponse":" MITUNGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773634367","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773634367"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773635525","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773635522"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" IKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773636253","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773636253"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TUPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773639340","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773639339"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773640608","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773640606"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" ALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773641386","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773641385"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773642027","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773642027"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773642813","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773642813"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773643375","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773643374"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773644696","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773644695"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWAALIKA"," userResponse":" AKIWAALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773645228","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773645228"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773646473","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773646472"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" KUHUDHURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773647311","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773647311"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773647533","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773647533"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773648356","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773648356"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIJI"," userResponse":" KUJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773651122","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773651122"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773652377","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773652376"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," userResponse":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773652958","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773652957"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773653042","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773653042"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773653470","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773653469"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773654044","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773654044"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773654451","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773654451"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773655385","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773655385"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" AMBAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773656248","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773656248"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOKEA"," userResponse":" TULIPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773656828","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773656827"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773657078","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773657078"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773657849","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773657848"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773660885","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773660885"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773661768","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773661768"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773662896","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773662895"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773663377","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773663377"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773664252","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773664252"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUNDI"," userResponse":" KIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773664645","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773664645"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773665394","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773665393"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773666734","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773666733"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773667950","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773667950"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUREKEBISHE"," userResponse":" TUREKEBISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773668513","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773668512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773669154","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773669154"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773672627","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773672626"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" JUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773673841","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773673841"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773674706","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773674705"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPANDA"," userResponse":" AMEPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773675328","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773675328"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773676258","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773676258"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773676552","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773676551"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773677228","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773677227"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773678262","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773678261"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773679355","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773679355"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFISHA"," userResponse":" KUSAFISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773680001","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773680001"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773680159","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773680159"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773680577","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773680576"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773681292","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773681291"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773684441","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773684440"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773685014","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773685013"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773685194","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773685193"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773685970","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773685969"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKAMO"," userResponse":" MAKAMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773686786","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773686786"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773687762","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773687762"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773688739","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773688738"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773689741","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773689740"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773690503","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773690502"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUNGANA"," userResponse":" KUUNGANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773690703","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773690702"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773691336","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773691320"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773692146","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773692146"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773695174","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773695173"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773695766","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773695766"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773695879","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773695878"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.108","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773704009","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773704008"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 660a9011-6bcc-47fb-9f64-0ded0417da9f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773714740","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773714740"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 2c77add2-d91f-43fd-8013-3070671e7821"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-6-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773715268","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773715268"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 2c77add2-d91f-43fd-8013-3070671e7821"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-6-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773724794","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773724793"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e64223be-9ce8-4b71-82cc-4fad29dcf1dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_p-o-g"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773728758","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773728758"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e64223be-9ce8-4b71-82cc-4fad29dcf1dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_b-p-t"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773732177","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773732177"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e64223be-9ce8-4b71-82cc-4fad29dcf1dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_p-u-t"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773735655","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773735655"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e64223be-9ce8-4b71-82cc-4fad29dcf1dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_g-p-a"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773739150","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773739150"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e64223be-9ce8-4b71-82cc-4fad29dcf1dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_s-p-j"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773743678","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773743677"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e64223be-9ce8-4b71-82cc-4fad29dcf1dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_a-e-p"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773747481","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773747480"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e64223be-9ce8-4b71-82cc-4fad29dcf1dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_p-i-f"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773751131","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773751131"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e64223be-9ce8-4b71-82cc-4fad29dcf1dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-g-p"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773756726","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773756726"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e64223be-9ce8-4b71-82cc-4fad29dcf1dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-g-p"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773760999","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773760998"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e64223be-9ce8-4b71-82cc-4fad29dcf1dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_p-m-n"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773764852","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773764852"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e64223be-9ce8-4b71-82cc-4fad29dcf1dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_z-p-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773770634","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773770634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e64223be-9ce8-4b71-82cc-4fad29dcf1dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_p_z-p-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773898087","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773898086"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e64223be-9ce8-4b71-82cc-4fad29dcf1dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.109"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_p_z-p-e"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773898189","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773898189"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 127254b7-c4c5-4bbf-bc72-bc6603adaf82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773907247","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773907247"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 127254b7-c4c5-4bbf-bc72-bc6603adaf82"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773917071","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773917071"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 86720274-770a-426c-8326-d4d2501e39de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_6-0-2"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773922174","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773922174"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 86720274-770a-426c-8326-d4d2501e39de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-3-7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773927485","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773927485"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 86720274-770a-426c-8326-d4d2501e39de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_8-2-3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773932388","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773932388"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 86720274-770a-426c-8326-d4d2501e39de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-7-0"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773937227","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773937227"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 86720274-770a-426c-8326-d4d2501e39de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_9-4-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773942396","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773942396"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 86720274-770a-426c-8326-d4d2501e39de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_4-5-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773949874","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773949874"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 86720274-770a-426c-8326-d4d2501e39de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_9-4-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773955346","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773955346"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 86720274-770a-426c-8326-d4d2501e39de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-8-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773962234","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773962234"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 86720274-770a-426c-8326-d4d2501e39de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_5-7-8"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773967928","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773967928"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 86720274-770a-426c-8326-d4d2501e39de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-2-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773973557","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773973555"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 86720274-770a-426c-8326-d4d2501e39de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-2-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543773978279","data":{"timestamp":" 1543773978279"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 86720274-770a-426c-8326-d4d2501e39de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-2-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774146306","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774146305"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 86720274-770a-426c-8326-d4d2501e39de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-2-9"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774146417","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774146417"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 2c63c744-2e14-4e2b-8c02-2a2f58cd5350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_33"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo usishangae unapoliona pua la nguruwe jinsi lilivyo kwa sababu limekuwa hivyo tangu wakati huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774152113","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774152112"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 2c63c744-2e14-4e2b-8c02-2a2f58cd5350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_33"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo usishangae unapoliona pua la nguruwe jinsi lilivyo kwa sababu limekuwa hivyo tangu wakati huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774158652","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774158652"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 2c63c744-2e14-4e2b-8c02-2a2f58cd5350"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_33"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo usishangae unapoliona pua la nguruwe jinsi lilivyo kwa sababu limekuwa hivyo tangu wakati huo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774166949","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774166948"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774170536","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774170535"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774175278","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774175278"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774179089","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774179088"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774182628","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774182628"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774186011","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774186011"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774189601","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774189601"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774192985","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774192984"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774196140","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774196140"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774199888","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774199888"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774203532","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774203532"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774207036","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774207036"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774210358","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774210358"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774214153","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774214153"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774218033","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774218033"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774222930","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774222930"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774226588","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774226588"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774230354","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774230354"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774234424","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774234424"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774238363","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774238363"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774243764","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774243764"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774247559","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774247559"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774252295","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774252295"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774256780","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774256780"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774262550","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774262549"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774437275","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774437274"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" bb7cc9c8-1df2-4d91-be74-0b407263fe50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774437393","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774437393"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" ed58695b-34fb-4b8a-a2dd-c74b9e6edec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOTOKEA"," userResponse":" KILICHOTOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774447513","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774447512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" ed58695b-34fb-4b8a-a2dd-c74b9e6edec0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Unafikiri nini kilichotokea?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774481575","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774481575"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774495739","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774495739"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774505110","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774505110"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774514078","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774514077"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774514497","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774514496"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774516164","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774516163"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774526206","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774526206"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774526408","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774526407"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774535642","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774535641"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774544854","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774544854"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774552650","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774552649"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774561677","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774561677"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774577597","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774577597"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774586346","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774586346"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774599259","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774599259"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774601347","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774601347"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774609999","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774609998"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 42c1db04-76fe-48a7-a65f-7810952f6d56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774620750","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774620750"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774627711","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774627711"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774629266","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774629266"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" radhi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADHI"," userResponse":" RADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774633951","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774633950"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" radhi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADHI"," userResponse":" RADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774635521","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774635521"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" runinga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774641153","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774641153"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" runinga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774642717","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774642717"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ruka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUKA"," userResponse":" RUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774649423","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774649422"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ruka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774651058","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774651058"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ramani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAMANI"," userResponse":" RAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774654675","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774654674"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ramani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAMANI"," userResponse":" RAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774656383","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774656383"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" rinda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774663825","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774663825"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" rinda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774665479","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774665479"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" redio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REDIO"," userResponse":" REDIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774669836","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774669836"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" redio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REDIO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774675975","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774675974"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" rangi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774680066","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774680066"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" rangi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774681636","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774681636"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" raha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHA"," userResponse":" RAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774685407","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774685407"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" raha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.56","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774687424","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774687423"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" raha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774687603","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774687603"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" raha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774722787","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774722786"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 48bc3b47-9695-4e61-91bb-f383f228ea0b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" raha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774722867","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774722867"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" ab6523fc-9f55-4309-861d-da3673897dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774729020","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774729020"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" ab6523fc-9f55-4309-861d-da3673897dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774735982","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774735982"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" ab6523fc-9f55-4309-861d-da3673897dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774750578","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774750577"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" ab6523fc-9f55-4309-861d-da3673897dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774761509","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774761508"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" ab6523fc-9f55-4309-861d-da3673897dd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774761677","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774761677"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 9e54ba7b-1912-48e3-b2cb-22410ab634d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774771078","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774771078"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 9e54ba7b-1912-48e3-b2cb-22410ab634d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774778378","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774778378"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 9e54ba7b-1912-48e3-b2cb-22410ab634d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774785807","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774785804"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" 9e54ba7b-1912-48e3-b2cb-22410ab634d7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774827863","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774827863"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e623faea-d8c3-499e-adad-a68767276502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774830941","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774830941"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e623faea-d8c3-499e-adad-a68767276502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774892511","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774892511"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e623faea-d8c3-499e-adad-a68767276502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774923125","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774923125"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e623faea-d8c3-499e-adad-a68767276502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774948480","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774948480"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e623faea-d8c3-499e-adad-a68767276502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774952916","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774952916"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e623faea-d8c3-499e-adad-a68767276502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543774964258","data":{"timestamp":" 1543774964257"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_204042"," gameId":" e623faea-d8c3-499e-adad-a68767276502"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}